<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chiamaka&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>http://chiamaka.github.io/blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chiamaka&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 15:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://chiamaka.github.io/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Creating An OSS Shopping Cart Component. Wanna Join In?</title>
      <link>http://chiamaka.github.io/blog/post/ui-mockup-created/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chiamaka.github.io/blog/post/ui-mockup-created/</guid>
      <description>So some time back I was roaming on the FB react-native community (if you don&amp;rsquo;t know that, click here) and I saw someone asking if there was a component like this and he posted up a photo of what he needed. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know if there was one but I had the idea that maybe I could build one.
So hear me out.
I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that maybe, just maybe, someone would be willing to work on this with me to make it a really helpful component.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating A Round Button With React Native Vector Icons</title>
      <link>http://chiamaka.github.io/blog/post/round-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chiamaka.github.io/blog/post/round-button/</guid>
      <description>I had a design I wanted to replicate and the button in this design is a round button and it has an icon in it.
Here is a snapshot
I immediately set out to accomplish the task. In my head, it was going to take less than 10 minutes. Ooh was I wrong. It took me the whole day to figure out.
I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make the process be less painful for you and for my future self (I tend to forget alot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial commit</title>
      <link>http://chiamaka.github.io/blog/post/initial-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 18:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chiamaka.github.io/blog/post/initial-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post on this blog.
Instead of the legendary &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; sentence for doing something for the first time in coding, I&amp;rsquo;ll call mine &amp;ldquo;Initial commit&amp;rdquo; after your first commit in git.
Today also signifies the day I was partially let go from my job, not fully. LOL, its complicated, I&amp;rsquo;ll most likely blog about it later.
Anyways, this is the first post on this blog and hopefully more to come.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>